rogersplus.ca 2007-06-23

# Welcome to Rogers Plus - Movies, Games, Wireless, Internet, Cable TV, Home Phone and more in-store for you

1\. This policy applies to Rogers Communications, Rogers Cable, Rogers Wireless and Rogers Media which are referred to here collectively as Rogers. At Rogers, the security and integrity of our customers' personal information is important to us. We take every reasonable measure necessary to protect the privacy of our customers while providing the high level communication services they expect. 

2\. Rogers' privacy practices are in accordance with all federal and provincial laws and regulations. We are compliant with the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (PIPEDA) and where applicable with the privacy rules established by the Canadian Radio-television and Telecommunications Commission (CRTC). 

3\. Rogers has in place privacy and security practices to safeguard our customers' personal information. These practices are reviewed, and if necessary revised, on a regular basis. Additionally, Rogers' employees receive privacy training and must comply with Rogers' privacy practices as a condition of employment. 

4\. Personal information collected by Rogers is information about an identifiable individual that may include such information as your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, financial information, birth date and any recorded complaints. 

5\. At Rogers, we collect customer information for one or more of the following purposes: 

  * To provide a positive customer experience, and deliver, bill for, and collect payment for products and services; 
  * To understand customer requirements and make information available regarding products and services offered by Rogers and its agents, dealers and related companies; 
  * To manage and develop Rogers business and operations; 
  * To meet legal and regulatory requirements; and 
  * To obtain credit information or provide it to others. 

6\. Rogers does not use or disclose personal information for purposes other than those for which it was collected, except with the consent of the individual or as required by law. Rogers retains personal information only as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes. 

7\. Rogers informs customers of the existence, use and disclosure of their personal information upon request and gives them access to their information. 

8\. Rogers ensures that customer information is accurate, complete and up-to-date. Customers can challenge the accuracy and completeness of the information and request amendments as appropriate. 

9\. Rogers companies share information with other Rogers companies or their agents and authorized dealers, in order to offer customers products and services that they may find attractive. Notices on sharing information are contained in each company's application forms, invoices and web sites. If customers do not want to be marketed with these products and services, they can contact Rogers (see How To Contact Rogers below). 

10\. Additional information on your privacy is located in the Frequently Asked Questions section of [www.rogers.com/video](http://www.rogers.com/video) under the Category of Privacy.

11\. A senior company officer has been appointed as the Chief Privacy Officer at Rogers. The Chief Privacy Officer is accountable for all personal information at Rogers. You may contact the Chief Privacy Officer at: 

**By Mail:**   
Chief Privacy Officer  
Rogers Group of Companies  
333 Bloor Street East  
Toronto, ON  
M4W 1G9

**By E-mail:**  

12\. Customers that wish to:   

  * obtain more information about Rogers Commitment to Privacy; 
  * access, or obtain more information about, their personal information held by Rogers; or 
  * make a privacy-related complaint; 

may contact a Rogers customer service representative who, if necessary, will refer the customer to the Rogers Chief Privacy Officer. 

13\. The Office of the Privacy Commissioner of Canada oversees Rogers' personal information handling practices. If your privacy concerns are not addressed to your satisfaction by Rogers you may contact the Office of the Privacy Commissioner of Canada for further guidance:

**By Phone:** 1-800-282-1376 or 613-995-8210  
**By Fax:** 613-947-6850  
**By E-mail:** [info@privcom.gc.ca](mailto:info@privcom.gc.ca)  
**Website:** [www.privcom.gc.ca](http://www.privcom.gc.ca/)

**How to Contact Rogers**

**Customers of Rogers Cable and Rogers Wireless**

Customers can have their account marked "Do Not Contact" by visiting Rogers On-line Self Service at [www.rogers.com](http://www.rogers.com/) and selecting "Manage My Marketing Permissions” under "Your On-line Profile”. Alternatively, you can contact a Rogers' customer service representative at 1-888-899-1188.

**Subscribers to Rogers Media consumer magazines**

Notices about "Subscriber Services" that appear in each consumer magazine explain how to change your "Mail Preference" for receiving mailings from other organizations. To have your mailing address excluded from mailings by other organizations, provide your subscriber information in one of the following ways: 

**By E-mail:** [rmpublishing@indas.ca](mailto:rmpublishing@indas.ca)

**By Mail:**   
Privacy Request   
Magazine Subscriber Services   
Box 860   
Markham, ON  
L3P 8H8

**By Phone:** (905) 946-0084 

**By Fax:** (905) 946-1679 

**Registered users of Rogers Media web sites and e-mail newsletters**

You can update your "Marketing Permissions" by establishing a user profile. From the web site, click on "Register" to establish a profile or on "Login" to update your permissions.

Back to top. Rogers Video has created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site. 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to gather broad, aggregated demographic information. Our site may use cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, and for the other purposes set out below: 

  * We use cookies to remind us who you are and to find your account information in our database when you access a service so you do not need to log in at every visit. This helps us to provide you with service tailored to your specific needs and interests. A cookie is created when you register for a service. 
  * We use cookies to estimate our audience size. Your browser is given a unique cookie that helps us determine whether yours is a repeat visit or a first visit. 
  * We use cookies to determine the browser the visitor uses so the site can be designed to work properly with the most common versions of different browsers. 
  * Advertisers that place ads with Rogers.com/video may use cookies 

Our site's registration forms require users to give us a unique username and password. To post a message in the site using an e-form, an email address is also required. 

This site contains links to third party sites. Rogers.com/video is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. Rogers.com/video co-branded sites and content partner sites may have privacy policies independent of Rogers.com/video. This Privacy Policy extends only to data collected on pages hosted on Rogers.com/video servers. Rogers.com/video may share aggregate information with trading partners, co-branded sites, and advertisers. However, this aggregated information does not contain personally identifiable information. 

Our online surveys and the contests on our site may ask visitors for such information as contact information (like their email address), financial information (like their investment portfolio holdings), and demographic information (like their postal code, age or income level). We may use contact data from our surveys or contests to send information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners, sponsors or advertisers. The customer's contact information may also be used to contact the visitor when necessary and may be shared with other affiliated companies within the Rogers Group of Companies who may want to contact our visitors. Only the Rogers Group of Companies has access to your personal information. Users may opt-out of receiving future e-mail communications. Please see the choice/opt-out section below. 

Demographic and profile data is used to tailor our visitor's experience at our site and display the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis only. 

**Public Forums**

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**Security**

This site has reasonable security measures in place to protect against loss, misuse and interception by third parties. The Rogers Group of Companies assumes no liability for interception, alteration or misuse of information transmitted over the Internet. 

**Children's Guidelines**

This site is not marketed to or directed towards children. Nevertheless, it is possible for children to publicly post or distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent within chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups. No communication, however, will be sent to anyone or information collected from anyone who indicates that they are younger than 16 years old without their parents' permission. 

**Choice/Opt-Out**

In the Registration process where we request information about the visitor, our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving email or other forms of communications from the Rogers Group of Companies. 

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, you can contact: 

**By Mail:**  
Chief Privacy Officer  
Rogers Communications Inc.  
333 Bloor Street East  
Toronto, ON  
M4W 1G9 

**By E-mail:**  

Last Revised: November 13, 2006 Version: 2006-2

Back to top.
